<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Ragam</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contents">Contents</string>
    <string name="workshops_heading">Workshops</string>
    <string name="prodezza_heading">Prodezza</string>
    <string name="competitions_heading">Competitions</string>
    <string name="competitions_contact">+918089219732</string>
    <string name="workshops_contact">+918089219732</string>
    <string name="prodezza_contact">+918089219732</string>
    <string name="eluveitie_description">This Ragam, we promise you an epic night,
        an experience like never before. We push new boundaries and bring to you,
        for the first time in South India, from halfway across the world, Swiss folk metal band,
        ELUVEITIE. Along with the typical lead, rhythm, base guitars and drums,
        Eluveitie continues to incorporate an armada of instruments that give their
        folk metal that really unique Celtic sound.</string>
    <string name="ankit_description">It is the electrifying crowd,
        the charge in the atmosphere and the sheer energy as you scream out that makes
        Ragam a memory worth saving. Create another memory on -th March, as Ragam\'15
        proudly presents Ankit Tiwari, for the first time, on the largest stage in south India.
        Immerse yourself in music, as you are regaled by the versatile singer of famous
        tracks like Galliyan and the evergreen Sun Rahai Tu.</string>
    <string name="third_proshow">Ragam presents, DJ Diego Miranda, all set to tear up the decks with his Indian debut at NIT Calicut.
Get ready for a night of pure ebullience as he transcends minds and hijacks your feet. Come indulge in an experience like never before as the base becomes your heartbeat and the rhythm your movement</string>
    <string name="reach_us">By Rail:\nDirect trains/coaches are available from Calicut to the major centres in India which include New Delhi, Jammu Tawi, Gorakhpur, Bombay, Calcutta, Gowhatti, Hyderabad, Bangalore, Madras, Ahmedabad, Indore, Trichy, Mangalore, Trivandrum and Varanasi. The Calicut bound trains take deviation from the main Madras-Cochin route from Palghat Junction or Shornur Junction. You can reach NIT Calicut by taxi from the Kozhikode (Calicut) Railway station and the taxi fare is approximately Rs. 500/- OR You can reach NIT Calicut by autorikshaw from the Kozhikode (Calicut) Railway station and the fare is approximately Rs. 400/-\n\nBy Road:\nJust follow the yellow brick road. Just kidding! You can reach NIT Calicut by taxi from the Kozhikode (Calicut) bus station (KSRTC or private bus station) and the taxi fare is approximately Rs. 500/- You can reach NIT Calicut by autoriksha from the Kozhikode (Calicut) bus station (KSRTC or private bus station) and the fare is approximately Rs. 400/-  OR  You can reach NIT Calicut by bus from Kozhikode (Calicut) bus station (KSRTC or private bus station). From these bus stations go to Palayam Bus station by taking an Autoriksha (fare :Rs.15/ ) and take a bus to NIT Calicut (buses to Mukkam, Areekkode, etc. via Kunnamangalam) and get down at NIT Calicut bus stop.</string>
    <string name="ragam">This is not just a fest, but the grandest of them all
Where the best of the best find knighted in fame\'s hall
Dot your i\'s and cross your it\'s; the less fortunate gape
\'Cause it\'s really happening, so Don Your Capes</string>

</resources>
